BU Records: Museum Studies Department, Inclusive: 1978-1997, undated, Bulk: 1990-1997
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: Museum Studies Department
Inclusive: 1978-1997, undated, Bulk: 1990-1997
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/355
Baylor University
28 document boxes.
BU Records: Museum Studies Department contains a variety of materials from the museum studies department at Baylor University, primarily correspondence as well as administrative records.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Excellent.
Biography/Profile
Baylor University's Museum Studies Department has been educating students in the field of museology since 1979. In that year, undergraduate courses were taught by employees of the Strecker Museum. By 1984, the program had received enough interest that the number of classes offered increased and the program expanded, allowing students to pursue either an undergraduate degree in Museum Studies. In 1993, Baylor officially recognized the museum studies program as an academic department. During that same year, the department launched its graduate degree program and offered students the option to pursue a Masters of Arts in Museum Studies with a concentration in administration. The program continues to operate today, offering courses to both undergraduates and graduate students but only granting master degrees.
Scope and Content
BU Records: Museum Studies Department consists of materials from 1978-1997 with some undated items. The records reflect the administrative and academic activities of the department, which was associated with the Strecker Museum. In particular, a large portion of collection contains materials from T. Lindsay Baker, who served as curator of the Governor Bill and Vera Daniel Historic Village, a departmental lecturer, and director of Academic Programs and Graduate Studies.
Series I. Correspondence contains letters that T. Lindsay Baker sent and received during the years of 1990 to 1997 as well as administrative correspondence from the Strecker Museum and Museum Studies Department. Series II. Administrative Records contains administrative records from the department such as student and employee information. Series III. Strecker Museum contains materials related specifically to the Strecker Museum and its relation to the department.
Arrangement
Prior to processing, this collection came organized in labeled folders with titles and date ranges. Some of the materials, such as the correspondence, were organized by month and year. The remaining materials were organized by subject and date. Most folder titles were retained during processing.
Currently, the collection is arranged in three series: I. Correspondence, II. Administrative Records, and III. Strecker Museum.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/355. Acquired 0-00-00
Related Resources
Related references
“Museum studies major — first of its kind.” Baylor Lariat, 1978 October 31.
Cheung, Catherine. “Graduate school to offer new degrees”. Baylor Lariat, 1993 March 31.
Smith, Calvin B. Interview by Leslee Elliot & Becky Shulda. 2007 April 17 in Austin, Texas. Transcript. Baylor University Institute for Oral History, Waco, TX.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- Museum Studies Department.; Baylor University -- Records and correspondence.; Strecker Museum -- History.
Subjects
Baker, T. Lindsay.; Education, Higher -- Texas -- Waco.; Museums -- Texas -- Waco.; Museums -- Texas.; Records (Documents)
Genres
Correspondence.
- Correspondence, 1990-1997; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Excellent.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains correspondence from T. Lindsay Baker, who was the curator of the Gov. Bill and Vara Daniel Historic Village, a lecturer in the department, and director of Academic Programs and Graduate Studies. It also contains correspondence from the museum studies department and the Strecker Museum. The series is in excellent condition.
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 January (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 February (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 February (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 March (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 April (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 April (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 May (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 May (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 June (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 June (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 July (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 July (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 August (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 August (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 September (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 September (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 October (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 October (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 November (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 November (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1990 December (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1990 December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 January (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 February (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 February (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 March (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 March (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 April (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 April (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 May (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 May (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 June (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 June (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 July (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 July (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 August (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 August (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 September (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 September (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 October (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 October (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1991 November (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1991 November (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 November (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1991 December (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1991 December (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 January (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) Winter 1992 Staff Retreat, 1992 January (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 January (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 February (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 February (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 March (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 March (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1992 June (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1992 June (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 June (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 August (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 August (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 September (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 September (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1992 October (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1992 October (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 October (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1992 November (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 November (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1992 December (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1992 December (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) Winter Long-Range Planning Retreat, 1992 December (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1992 December (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 January (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 January (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 February (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 February (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 March (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 March (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 April (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 April (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 May (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 May (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 June (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 June (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 July (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 July (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 August (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 August (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 September (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 September (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1993 October (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1993 October (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 October (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1993 November (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1993 November (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 November (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1993 December (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1993 December (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 January (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 January (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 January (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1994 February (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker, 1994 February (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 March (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 March (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 March (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 April (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 April (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 April (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 May (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 May (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 May (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1994 June (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 June (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1994 July (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 July (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1994 August (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 August (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 September (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 September (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 September (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 September (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1994 October (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 October (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 November (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 November (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1994 November (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1994 November (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1994 December (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1994 December (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1995 January (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1995 January (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 January (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1995 February (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1995 February (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 February (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 March (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 March (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 April (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 April (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 May (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 May (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 June (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 June (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 July (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 July (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1995 August (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1995 August (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 August (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1995 September (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2), 1995 September (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 September (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 October (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 October (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 November (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 November (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1995 December (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1995 December (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1996 January (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1996 January (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 January (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1996 February (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1996 February (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 February (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1996 March (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 March (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1996 April (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 April (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1996 April (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1996 May (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 May (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1996 June (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 June (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1996 July (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 July (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1996 August (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1996 August (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 August (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1996 September (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1996 September (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 September (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1996 October (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1996 October (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1996 October (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1996 October (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1996 November (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1996 November (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 November (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1996 December (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1996 December (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1997 January (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1997 January (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1997 January (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1997 February (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1997 February (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1997 March (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1997 March (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1997 April (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1997 April (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1997 April (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 1 of 2, 1997 May (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker) 2 of 2, 1997 May (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1997 May (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1997 June (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1997 June (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Received (T. L. Baker), 1997 July (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Museum Studies — Letters Sent (T. L. Baker), 1997 July (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - T. Lindsay Baker — MST Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - T. Lindsay Baker - MST Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - T. Lindsay Baker - MST Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Administrative Records, 1981-1997, undated; 2
  This series contains the administrative files of the museum studies department which includes financial records, student and faculty records, and course information. The series is in excellent condition.
  - List of Bachelor Graduates, 1981-1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Videodisc Materials, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Internship Programs (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Internship Programs (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Exit Exams, 1990-1994, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - University Research Committee, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Outside Funding — National Endowment for the Humanities (1 of 2), 1992-1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Outside Funding — National Endowment for the Humanities (2 of 2), 1992-1997 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Inventory of Course Listings, 1992, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Resumes of Visiting Faculty, 1992-1993, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)